<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<extension version="3.1" type="plugin" group="content" method="upgrade">
    <name>SSOFB Columns</name>
    <creationDate>May 2014</creationDate>
    <author>Andy gaskell @ SSOFB</author>
    <authorEmail>ag@ssofb.co.uk</authorEmail>
    <authorUrl>http://ssofb.co.uk</authorUrl>
    <copyright>This extension in released under the GNU/GPL License - http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.html</copyright>
    <license>GNU General Public License version 2 or later; see LICENSE.txt</license>
    <version>1.0</version>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2>SSOFB Columns</h2>
    <p>This is a very simple bootrap column plug-in. It suports Bootstrap fluid responsive layout.  It assumes you have a bootstrap template, like Protostar.</p>
    <p>At the relevant viewport, typically 768 pixels wide, the columns will switch from being side-by-side to being on-top of each other.</p>
    <p>Primary syntax, this plug-in supports 2, 3, 4, 6 or 12 columns, as per the bootstrap 12 grid system</p>
    <p>Seconday syntax, by placing {split} in your content the text prior with be put in a span8 div whilst the text after will be put in a span4 div.</p>
    <p>Tertiary syntax, by placing {splitleft} in your content the text prior with be put in a span4 div whilst the text after will be put in a span8 div.</p>
    <p>These syntaxes cannot be used together.</p>
    
    <p>To use it, just use the following syntaxes in your articles:</p>
    
    <p>Primary syntax:</p>  
    <pre>
    {cols}
    This is my first column, as much text as you like here. 
    {colbr}
    This is my second column, as much text as you like here, or images by the way. 
    {colbr}
    This is my third column, content can be whatever. 
    {/cols} 
    </pre>

    <p>Secondary syntax:</p>      
    <pre>
    This is my first column, it'll be span8 blah blah 
    {split}
    This is my second column, it'll be span4 blah blah 
    </pre>    

    <p>Tertiary syntax:</p>          
    <pre>
    This is my first column, it'll be span4 blah blah 
    {splitleft}
    This is my second column, it'll be span8 blah blah 
    </pre>            
    
    The code is in GitHub at https://github.com/AndyGaskell/ssofb_columns
    ]]></description>
    <scriptfile>ssofbcolumns.php</scriptfile>
    <params>  
    </params>
    <config>
    </config>
    <files>
        <filename plugin="ssofbcolumns">ssofbcolumns.php</filename>
        <filename plugin="ssofbcolumns">index.html</filename>		
    </files>
</extension>
